

NESRINE AOUINTI

FullStack Web Developer

nesrineaouinti.dev@gmail.com 💌

Nabeul - Tunisie

in /in/aouintinesrine/

@Nesrine Aouinti

ABOUT ME

Software engineer with over two years of experience in web development. passionate about innovation and new technologies, I am always ready to take on new challenges and goals! Motivated to develop my technical skills and adapt perfectly to teamwork.

ACADEMIC EDUCATION

The Mediterranean Polytechnic School: EPM **SEPTEMBER 2021 - JUNE 2024**

Engineering program in computer engineering. Specialization: business intelligence

Institute of Information and Communication SEPT 2018 - JUNE 2021 Technology (ISTIC)

Bachelor's degree in Computer Science and **Telecommunications**

Dar Chabanne High School, Dar Chaaben

Baccalaureate in Mathematics

JUNE 2018

SKILLS

- Basic languages: HTML / CSS / JavaScript / PHP / python
- Libraries: ¡Query React.js
- CSS frameworks: Bootstrap / Tailwind CSS
- CSS preprocessors: SASS / LESS
- · Front-end frameworks: Next.js Angular
- Back-end frameworks: Laravel Django Express.js
- Database communication languages: SQL NOSQL
- Databases: MySQL PostgreSQL MongoDB
- · Version control tools: GIT
- · Version control platforms: GitLab GitHub
- Deployment platforms: Heroku Vercel
- DevOps: Docker
- · Project management : Scrum Jira clickup

ACADEMIC PROJECTS

- Development of Project Management Tools (Web application) / Technologies: React.js / Express.js / MongoDB
- Development of a Website with HTML / CSS / **Javascript**
- Development of an E-commerce platform for computer equipment management (PHP / HTML / CSS / SQL)

CERTIFICATIONS

- IBM Academic Certificat February 2020 / "Cloud Application Developer 2019 Mastery Award "- UNIQUE ID :9887-158016777
- IBM Academic Certificate- February 2021 / Big Data Engineer v2 Mastery Award (2018) - UNIQUE ID: 3382-1612-1716-3680

INTERESTS

Reading | Music | Camping

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

- Ostelflow FullStack Web Developer Nov 2022 Present
- · Write clean and efficient code for a responsive user interface with Next.js and react js.
- Collaborate with UX/UI designers to enhance the user experience.
- · Develop and manage databases for efficient data storage and retrieval.
- Create functional server-side applications.
- Write efficient APIs with Django REST to facilitate communication between the front-end and back-end.
- · Implement security measures and data protection to ensure data
- Work with ERPNext WebHooks by processing incoming data with Django.
- Aftercode Web Developer August 2021 - October 2022
- · Developing and implementing user interfaces using React.js and Next.js.
- · Creating showcase and e-commerce websites with Next.js, while enhancing their SEO.
- · Developing and implementing REST APIs.
- · Improving user experience (UI) with Next.js.
- Deploying projects on Vercel and Heroku platforms.
- Twedoo End of Studies Internship (PFE) Fev 2021 Juin. 2021
- · Designing and developing a web application for delivery management Technologies: Angular 11 / Laravel 6 / MySQL
- Neopolis Developpement improvement Internship

AUGUST 2022 - SEPTEMBER 2020

- Development of a mailing service with PHP
- · Authentication module
- Automatic email sending using the SMTP protocol

FREELANCE MISSIONS

- · Development of an application for complete management of a Delivery Company: client management / Fleet management / Driver management / Google Maps API / Company information configuration. Technologies: Angular 14 / Express.js / MongoDB
- Development of a solution for digital signage, remote content management of your screen. Technologies: React.js / Express.js / MongoDB
- Development of a website for a computer agency -Technologies: Next.js / Django
- · Development a Front end of innovative solutions for enhancing online presence and customer engagement.(GiftyShop)